I am Mai Haruta. This is Kaon from Kyushu Girls' Quota.
This is the second half part of the dialogue looking back on Tokyo Yakan Land vol. 2.
Thank you very much. Thank you for watching.
Here is the second half.
In the second half, I would like to look back on the day of the performance,
First of all, when I entered the venue, I wondered if I could set up the stage during the rehearsal,
I was told before, on January 9, that the audience would be there.
When I was told on January 9, I thought it was going to be close.
But I had already heard that it was close,
But now I see that it is really close.
I thought, "I've never seen such a diverse group of people perform at such a distance from each other.
It was really fresh for me,
Also, when it came time for the show.
When I looked at the audience, there were people who could see well into the back of the stage.
The spirit was good, of course, but I could see their faces as well.
When I pointed to them, they knew it was me.
I enjoyed that reaction.
The atmosphere was a little homey, but at the same time
There was a lot of enthusiasm.
There was some kind of playacting part.
There was a song and a play.
The reactions to the play part were amazing.
You could feel the distance directly from the audience.
Yes, yes, yes.
But when I heard your laughter
I was so happy.
It was so much fun!
As we got closer to the show
I felt that everyone's character was getting stronger and stronger
I felt like my character was getting stronger and stronger.
A little bit over the top.
Yeah.
But before...
In the radio booth.
I was a girl named Kasuga Mai, and I was the personality of a radio show called "You and My Pace.
I was really good with her, and we were just offstage, and we were in the Yokado area, next to the sound guy, and a woman came out from nearby.
And then you'd come out near the women's area, right next to the sound guy.
So when they first came out there, everyone kind of looked twice.
It was funny because when they first came out, they kind of looked twice.
It's a surprise, but it's also interesting to see the way their eyes change from one place to the next.
Everyone was looking at the stage, and it was a patching theme depending on my part.
So I was in a situation where I didn't know when it was going to come out because it came out every once in a while in each part.
I didn't know when it was going to come out.
It's like when you stand up like this, you're like Elian.
It's like the people around you are getting popular, but the person closest to you hasn't noticed yet, or something like that.
And the moment they become popular, they fall down.
Why?
Oh, that's possible? Like, "Thank you very much.
I don't remember that.
I did.
Kanon is a girl named Kanon Otomo.
Haniba, Kana-chan, Angel, Narita, and Kana.
Sahorn is doing an interview with Angel Wakabayashi Saho in Doridori.
It was a harpoon, wasn't it?
High school girls.
It was pretty much a high school girl's caper.
I mean, it was a bit of a quirky thing.
I knew it.
She played the role of Harima Kana-chan and her best friend.
So we started off meeting for the first time.
We had about half an hour to talk after our first meeting.
We had about 30 minutes to talk.
Right.
I was asked to set it up early.
We're going to be best friends.
So, like, let's get to know each other, and then we'll have a 30-minute conversation.
You want me to make a video of that?
The café where we became best friends.
In the corner of the rehearsal room.
Like, "What's your favorite food?" "What's your favorite color?
Or what their favorite animal is when they meet for the first time.
Anyway, we'll start with the information.
We both give each other profiles.
What do you like in common?
Rabbits and eating animals.
Oh!
That's what we have in common.
That's what we have in common and that they're cute.
It just came out.
So let's see what they have in common.
I'm going to pin on a character that's an eating animal, a rabbit.
Yes!
When we were in high school, there was a scene where we both wore pins in our hair.
There was a scene in high school where they were walking around Harajuku with them in their hair.
That's how far we went!
Ten years later, Kana is an actress.
Kana-chan is an actress and she wears a bunny pin here when she's on the radio.
When I was singing secret bass
I put a rabbit pin here when I sing "Secret Bass".
I was actually thinking of it like Urasen, like, "I wonder if anyone noticed...
It's an answer to a question, so that's what I had in mind.I just thought of it that way because it's an answer to a question.
I like rabbits when we're talking together. I like tameco animals. I didn't know that.
Oh, I thought it was a hair-piercer. That's where you knew.
That's what we both like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's why I took a gander at it.
You're right. It's a shame.
By the way, the origin of the name of the role...
The name "Otomo" comes from Prime Minister Otomo, a warlord associated with Fukuoka, and "Otomo" comes from the name of the prime minister.
The cheap setting is really nice! Emo, definitely emo!
I'm sure it's emo... and both of them made their fingers come true... so did all five of us... oh, I forgot...
I forgot, I don't have any scum in my role, so I'm interviewing Summers, who's the cup of Saori Wakabayashi...
I've heard that I'm Ms. Ootori's "Ore" from the two of you, Ms. Kasuga, Ms. Wakabayashi, Ms. Matsuwari and Ms. Ootori.
I wrote a lot of different radio segments.
I also wrote about various radio corners, including the popular topic of "Oshinokono.
You know, she noticed.
I was really into it, and more importantly, when the show went on the air...
And more than anything, there were places where they would look at it and laugh.
Your reactions were really funny.
Makana-chan was really excited and her voice was loud.
And when it came to the actual performance, she was tens of times more excited than in the rehearsal.
I knew I couldn't let her down.
We influenced each other in a good way.
We had the mindset that it was going to be a knocker night for a long time.
And when it came to the real thing
I was in the radio booth on the end.
I wasn't looking directly at the audience, but I was listening to everyone's voices and filming their reactions.
but I was listening to everyone's voices and filming their reactions.
The gals were really gals.
She was a gal, wasn't she?
She really was.
And during the rehearsal, Saohkyun was on the stage, too, but he was gradually coming out of his shell.
It seemed to stand out because of the character of the role.
Makachan has this image of a gal, but Rinna T doesn't have that image, so it was refreshing to see her as a gal.
You only get to see that side of her. She's got a real face.
I liked it there, Kanon-chan.
Kanon-chan said she's going to do her best
After she said she'll do her best.
I'll do my best.
And then she started talking, and I told her she shouldn't say that.
I stood up on my feet and said...
"I can't say it's going to be a company," he says.
I love it when he just bursts out.
That makes me happy.
It's a little bit...
I wanted to show my character, so I was really close to the audience, so I was making her really attractive when I was being all fidgety.
I was so surprised when I said that I was this kind of character, but what made me happy was that many people were reacting to my performance.
There were also some very strong scenes in the other scenes.
I don't know...
It was interesting to see the foreshadowing of what was to come.
Everyone's dreams came true.
And at the end, it ended up being a scene from a movie.
I thought it was interesting from the moment I read the script.
The more I read the script, the more I thought, "So that's what this is all about.
Deep technique
It was the acting part.
If I like that one too, I'll have to make a 70/70 mistake.
Kana-chan.
Hana-chan played the role of a doctor.
She gives Milati, who's now a mother, an injection.
But she failed the first time.
And after I told her not to fail in the nana-wari form...
I said, "Don't fail the sevenshot," and she succeeds one more time.
I failed in the sextuplet form, so...
It's decreasing.
And Milatee's smirk reads it.
It's nice, isn't it?
Like it's decreasing.
But it's still pretty scary when you actually tell it.
Scary.
It's because Kundara and Hana-chan do it that it's more interesting.
The personalities of the members and the characters combined to make it really interesting.
I think it's great that all the personalities came out.
And more than anything, singing and acting, singing and acting, there's a lot to remember.
I was like, "What's next?" "When am I going to change my clothes?
I feel a sense of accomplishment when I change my T-shirt and come out of the show like I'm in order nine up.
Yeah, it's really something. Even backstage, the members who finished their solos would say, "Good job.
They're like, "What's next?" They're like, "Good luck." I could see a real bond there.
It was like we all made it together.
It's like we all made it together.
I felt like we all worked together to create the show, and it was a lot of fun.
The first time we all started with the river, and the last time we all performed together, like Ambitious and Japan, it was really amazing.
The way the river rolled was amazing, wasn't it?
The river was amazing.
We all covered Ikebi48's River as the first song,
When the lights went on in the center of the stage, Wakachan Yasumori said, "That was so cool!
That was so cool!
Tokyo! Tokyo!
Ppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppp!
Yakanran!
What do you say?
It's kind of funny.Kind of funny, though.
Yakanran
They all look so cool.
I can't believe it!
But...
But they were so cool!
They were so cool!
You can tell from this distance.
I could see the audience
I could see the audience's reaction to the song.
And I could see the audience's reaction to "Staver".
I could also see some of the audience members bursting into tears when they heard the staver, and I was so happy to see their reactions.
It's a really simple word, but I'm glad I did it, and I'm glad I worked hard for it.
I saw how hard you guys were working and how you were struggling since the rehearsal, so...
I was so happy to see you guys working so hard and worrying so much since the rehearsal, so I was really happy to see that.
It was like, "I'm glad we were able to do it.
I was so happy that I could do it.
It was fun.
It was fun. More than anything, really.
I want to do it again.
The next day, I had just finished launching, and the day after that, I was saying this, so...,
It's all in the afterglow.
You've been talking a lot in the afterglow.
You've been talking a lot.
There was also an announcement at the end of the event,
Tokyo Yakaraland Vol. 3: The Rose of the Lamprey Tick
will be held on Wednesday, September 6 at Tokyo Kinema Club in Tokyo Uguisudani.
I'm looking forward to it... even during the rehearsals, we had a script, and we said we would announce it here in Manual 3.
They never told us who was going to be in the show, and they never told us who was going to be in the show, and they never told us who was going to be in the show.
We were...
We were so excited.
That's why we really wanted to know who was going to be in the Sony spin show at the same time as you.
We found out who was going to be in Sony's spin.
We found out who was going to be in the show.
Suddenly, we were joined by Tohoku-san
Waka Yasumori and Miyu Fujitani
Yuzuki Daikoku from Team Shachi
Yuzuki Daikoku
From Uka
Grahosiriju-chan
Battenshi Shoujo-tai
Sakura Shaka-chan
Crown Pup
Mitai-Agoki-chan
Andonai Nairuna-chan
Harimakana-chan
Kurumi Mori
When we were a former member of the group together, the leader of the group will be there.
Kurumi Hori, and Haru name, two people from outside of Starlust will be appearing.
Aika Hinui from Scene Sound and Maya Ayaha will be joining us.
That's great.
Ms. Ayaha is a former Takarazuka, currently an idol, and a YouTuber.
So I thought the male actors would come.
Maybe this title is also...
It's a title that says, "Oh, yes, that's right, isn't it?
It will be 3 months from now, but I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
The other thing is that Ayaka Kinoki, who is a member of Nyushon-san, has always been a big fan of girls' oku and Nyushon-san, even making 20,000 live performances.
The other day, Ayaka and I performed together.
They're pretty close.
Ayaka-chan is going to perform with us, so I'm already feeling like I should go for it.
Is Ayaka still in high school?
She's only 17.
But she's really cool.
But she's really cool. Can I go see her?
I want you to come see her.
I really hope you'll come see her at the last UPDY Japan event.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I used to be in Reine Takagi's group.
Our leader, Kurumi Mori, is doing her first service this time.
Vol. 1 is with Karin Negishi, who's the same age as me.
And here's Ishikawa. Why?
We're the third members from Hakonishi.
Kurumi, I think you can watch with peace of mind.
I'm really happy to see you all again.
Everyone's really...
Yuzuki-chan from our office is also in this show.
There were nine of us this time, but next time there will be twelve.
And it's going to be me.
I'm really looking forward to seeing you all again.
I hope you can look forward to seeing the nighttime performances, which will be different from the ones in Volume 2.
I hope you are looking forward to it.
I think the next volume will probably continue with volume 4 or 5,
Yes.
That's right. I hope you will join us, Kamo-chan.
By all means. We'll do it again.
I want to do it together again.
I want to.
You know, the two of us, we wanted to go out and sing,
I'm sure. I want to.Certainly. I want to do it.
I want to. I'd like to do it, but I'd like to be more fearless.
But I want you to be more fearless.
By all means. I want to do it again.
I'd like to do it again.
Lastly.... Last time, one by one...
Yes, I will.
If you have any messages or announcements for those who are watching, please let us know. Yes, I do.
This time, I really grew a lot in this Tokyo YakanLand, and I was able to perform with Shimoda-san's group, which really stimulated me a lot,
I think I was able to grow and develop. If you are interested in Kyushu Jyoshiryoku even a little bit at this Tokyo Yakan Land, please come and join us at one of the many festivals this summer,
We are looking forward to performing at many festivals this summer.
First of all, Spark 2023, Sekigahara, and Tahime Kassen,
We are also very much looking forward to TIFF2023,
We are also looking forward to performing at TIFF2023 and at Jam Expo.
I'm sure there will be many festivals where our staff members' groups will also perform,
If you think you can make Kyushu Girl's Power, we would be very happy if you could come to our festival.
Thank you very much.
You're going to want to see a lot of people, really!
Well, yes, I want to!
Well, I'll be seeing you again.
Thank you very much, Mr. Morium.
It's really, really nice to see
Each one of you
individuality and so on.
I think it was a great show.
I think it was a great live performance, and
I think that those who came
I think those who came to the show
I think we were able to I think we were able to do it.
I think everyone was so nice.
I think volume 3 and volume 4 will follow in the future.
I hope you can look forward to it.
I would like to make an announcement for the end of May.
What?
I will be performing in a reading play!
I'm going to be in a reading at the end of May!
I will be appearing in "Struggle in the Ice Age"!
From Thursday, June 29th to Sunday, July 2nd.
The theater is...
Cofraio Shinjuku Theatre, for a total of 8 performances.
This is my second time to perform in a Rotoku play.
I'm also excited about the fact that it's a bit of a dinosaur story.
Rehearsals will be starting soon, so I'll do my best.
I hope you will all come and see it.
I look forward to seeing you all.
I want to go see it.
You want to go?
I want to go.
Sounds like fun.
Well, you know, we all have our own thing going on.
I hope you'll check out the members' Twitter, Instagram, and various other social networking sites.
So, my partners so far have been Mai Handa and Hanon, who plays the role of Kyushu girl.
Thank you very much. Bye bye.